# TRAVIS MALONEY

15 Sandra Rd, London ON N5V 4X5 | 226-688-7969 | travis.maloney1@gmail.com

## Summary

Junior Web Developer with a background knowledge of Computer Science. Experience working independently to prioritize and track assignments and deadlines while interacting effectively with a team to achieve common objectives. Always maintain flexibility to adapt to changing environments while remaining focused on achieving desired results. Quick learner who is passionate about technology.

## Education

#### **Web Development Full-Time**

Jan 2016- Mar 2016

Brainstation Toronto, Ontario

### **Computer Science**

May 2015 – Dec 2016

University of Western Ontario London, Ontario

Completed 8 Computer Science courses towards a BSc. in Computer Science

#### **Human Resources Management Graduate Certificate**

2011-2012

Georgian College Barrie, Ontario

## **Bachelor of Management and Organizational Studies Specialization in Finance and Administration**

2007-2011

University of Western Ontario London, Ontario

# **Work Experience**

### **Customer Service Representative Financial Advisor**

May 2015 - September 2016 January 2013 - May 2015

Scotiabank, London, ON

- Utilized critical thinking skills and available resources to address customer inquiries and provided value-added solutions in addition to assisting with clients' explicit needs
- Actively listened to clients and utilized tools to develop and implement financial planning strategies to efficiently and effectively meet clients' financial goals while maximizing customer profitability

#### **Human Resources Assistant**

May 2012 - January 2013

Albarrie Canada Limited, Barrie, ON

- Collaborated with individuals from multiple departments, remaining flexible to ensure that desired results are achieved while maintaining a positive work environment with good morale
- Effectively communicated with internal and external stakeholders to achieve results that were in line with organizational strategy and goals

# TRAVIS MALONEY

15 Sandra Rd, London ON N5V 4X5 | 226-688-7969 | travis.maloney1@gmail.com

## **Community Involvement**

#### **Hack Western Participant**

2016/2017

University of Western Ontario, London, ON 2016 Winner of Organizing Team's Choice Award

#### **Public Arts Commissioner**

March 2010 - April 2011

University of Western Ontario, London, ON

- Aided the student life department in organizing, promoting, and maintaining a public art gallery
- Organized and executed Festival of the Arts, helping the University's Students' Council to achieve its goals of offering students engaging cultural programming

## Assistant Head Soph/Society of Off Campus Students Coordinator

January 2010 - April 2011

University of Western Ontario, London, ON

- Built strong relationships with incoming students and aided them in their post-secondary success
- Facilitated training for over two hundred orientation week volunteers
- Underwent leadership and diversity training through the Student Success Centre and the University Students' Council
- Helped select and lead a team of 45 volunteers from 350 applicants

## Peer Mentor, Leadership and Mentorship Program

September 2009 - April 2010

University of Western Ontario, London, ON

- Mentored and was a peer leader to 50 first year students
- Assisted first year students with their academics and transition to university
- Provided first year students with a variety of leadership opportunities and engaging programming

#### Courses

- COMPSCI 1026: Comp Sci Fundamentals I
- COMPSCI 1027: Comp Sci Fundamentals II
- COMPSCI 2208: Intro to Computer Organization and Architecture
- COMPSCI 2209: Applied Logic for Computer Science
- COMPSCI 2210: Data Structures and Algorithms
- COMPSCI 2211: Software Tools & Systems Programming
- COMPSCI 3319: Databases I
- COMPSCI 3357: Computer Networks I

# **Technologies**

- Git, Visual Studio Code, Linux (Ubuntu), TDD (Mocha), gulp.is, Object Oriented Programming
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Express, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Sass
- Previously used (> 6 months ago): Java, Android Studio, Python, Flask, MySQL, C, Eclipse